<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lqb2 &amp; co.</title>
    <description>transform yourself, transform the world — grace lee boggs</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 12:22:20 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 12:22:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.7</generator>
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Coaching Testimonial - Miriam M.</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h3 id=&quot;what-do-i-appreciate-about-lawrence-as-a-coach&quot;&gt;What do I appreciate about lawrence as a coach?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hands down, I appreciate Lawrence’s active listening and deep engagement with what I expressed as my goals, struggles, and challenges. While his practice had its own shape, it felt very much like Lawrence adapted his coaching practice to the goals that I wanted to achieve, the problems I identified, and the shifts I wanted to make (and learned that I wanted to make through coaching!). And the active listening I was so so key. Because there were things that I said through my coaching sessions that I did not realize were trends or reflective of larger blocks that needed to be shifted. Lawrence picked up on these things, and shared with me his reflections — always being careful to check whether his reflection resonated — and we processed these insights jointly. For that, I am deeply appreciative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;while-lawrence-supported-me-with-coaching-what-about-my-life-changed-or-shifted&quot;&gt;While lawrence supported me with coaching, what about my life changed or shifted?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big shift was my ability to identify the small blocks on my life that added up to the major blocks. For example, Lawrence and I processed my writing blocks. I thought of it as one huge challenge, when really it was a composite of many many tiny blocks, some of which I have been able to shift over the years, and others of which I am still working on. This framing—paying attention to the small things that make a big thing, and shifting small things, which can lead to a big impact—has been monumental in helping me move though situations that I previously found prohibitively challenging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/miriam-mack-58276223/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Miriam Mack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/coaching&quot;&gt;Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/16/coaching-testimonial-miriam.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/16/coaching-testimonial-miriam.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>events</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Coaching Testimonial - Jaco Cohen</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Lawrence is a special mix of enormous heart (e.g. deep listening, empathy), brilliant mind (e.g. insights, connections), and connected soul (e.g. groundedness, &lt;em&gt;big&lt;/em&gt; picture). What else could you want in a coach??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So much shifted when we were working together:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;awareness of negative self-talk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ability to feel what my gut’s telling me&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;feeling at peace about leaving work earlier / on time&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;regularly stepping back and planning at work&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;connection to my body&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;self-love&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jaco-cohen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jaco Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/coaching&quot;&gt;Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/13/coaching-testimonial-jaco.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/13/coaching-testimonial-jaco.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>events</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Coaching Testimonial - Huma G.</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Lawrence Barriner II has had a transformative effect on my life in the past few years. Our sessions have been spaced out across years, which has enabled a long-term re-imagining and re-visioning of what I think the trajectory of my life and purpose is in a given moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life-coaching is at times an inadequate term for what this process looks like, because while Lawrence asks provocative questions and we articulate goals together, the interaction always helps reorient how I think about who I am and what I think I want. Sometimes, he does this by facilitating a sort of ‘time travel’ where we visit future iterations of who I could be in my politics, what I could do through paid and unpaid labor, and with my kinship. Other times, he encourages me to create a RPG (role-playing game) in my mind so I can experience an embodied feeling of various archetypes of who I think I want to be, e.g. a teacher, a revolutionary, a writer, a parent. And once those personal, political, spiritual, communal goals are articulated, Lawrence has helped me organize my thoughts, times, and intentions to pursue a particular course of action through reflective practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes our conversations are very goal-oriented and other times, they are to disrupt the foundations upon which I have built those goals. A lot of this happens because Lawrence is willing to always share his journey, his learning, and his challenges through books and what has influenced him in a given moment. Lawrence is a “life coach” who coaches you through showing you how he tries to fully live his own life. And the remarkable thing has been that when we have set intentions, goals, and done these visioning exercises, many of the things that I had imagined actually came to be because working with him helped me open myself up to those particular goals. I am not sure if this is an exaggeration, but in my experience, usually within a year of me articulating an intention, my life transforms in such a manner that those intentions are realized. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
— &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jadaliyya.com/Author/9833&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Huma Gupta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/coaching&quot;&gt;Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/11/coaching-testimonial-huma.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/11/coaching-testimonial-huma.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>events</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Book Highlights</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;highlights.md&quot;&gt;see here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/07/highlights.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events/2020/10/07/highlights.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>events</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Book Highlights</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Here are some the highlights/notes from books I’ve read since ~2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1b2R-nzyBODuyE068x7dZIOccR71SQ2WvaP_jwjMKPjM/edit#heading=h.isk3d9mh6ws6&quot;&gt;My Grandmother’s Hands: Racialized Trauma and the Pathway to
Mending Our Hearts and Bodies by Resmaa Menakem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1lfwPP5pNCrIhgM9tU7turLta0ObTBWYQQIHorE_Ptvw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;How to Change Your Mind: What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence by Michael Pollan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Zp_8aM-i-ZcF1rpyIVHZXqtn-WZVEI3cOIEUTdvdCQ8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;M Archive - After The End of the World by Alexis Pauline Gumbs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/18LUDk8vFoIwk2V08A2Ozg6V_XCl6l4OhoX4vRhG2HMQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;What the Mystics Know: Seven Pathways to Your Deeper Self by Richard Rohr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fJXo7Vft9Q27ZxhLpYKi34LjloN8uv3jww97IB9SNJk/edit#heading=h.7eaf83x565lv&quot;&gt;Decolonizing Wealth: indigenous wisdom to heal divides and restore balance by Edgar Villanueva&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Xbl9Yyl0WMnoL9ZHtfIbTLrMKyfZs2PCF_X04cJO5w8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Of Water and the Spirit: Ritual, Magic, and Initiation in the Life of an African Shaman by Malidoma Patrice Some&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/spewil/bookclub&quot;&gt;Tell Me How Long the Train’s Been Gone
by James Baldwin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1BXNjEWNht46wTHFlymfWy00b15RJYk2Kl0dGqUBVCRo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Atomic Habits: An Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones by James Clear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1OFB88c6CzWG5kGXaccuTLzJV2MUjjH0lrA53lpcU8Uw/edit#heading=h.4krziu3nbdml&quot;&gt;Conflict Is Not Abuse - Overstating Harm, Community Responsibility, and the Duty of Repair by Sarah Schulman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/174kniuH2Y60yt0-pjfuAK-JAtSBXUJQ1kPhJkiTdqM0/edit#heading=h.n69fg0cdulli&quot;&gt;Power-Curve Society: The Future of Innovation, Opportunity and Social Equity in the Emerging Networked Economy by David Bollier, Raporteur&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NZ3eAyPmGUQ_qSy5VktgXa94AuG6TlpZtUanl3Ntnwc/edit&quot;&gt;Deep Work: Rules for Focused Success in a Distracted World
by Cal Newport&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deep gratitude to my friend, Leo Martinez, who has typed these up for years. ::praying hands emoji::&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/events/2020/08/04/highlights.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/events/2020/08/04/highlights.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>events</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Coaching</title>
          
          <author>lawrence@lqb2.co (lqb2 & co.)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;!-- &gt; If I love you, I have to make you conscious of the things you do not see. — James Baldwin --&gt;

&lt;!-- Main --&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;main&quot; class=&quot;alt&quot;&gt;

&lt;!-- One --&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;one&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;inner&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;You can check out the origin story of my coaching practice &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@lqb2/how-i-started-a-coaching-practice-c98e9f383d01&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;on Medium&lt;/a&gt; and lots of my other thoughts about productivity &lt;a href=&quot;https://lqb2.github.io/blog/tags/#productivity-ref&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;on my blog&lt;/a&gt;. Don't hesitate to send me questions!&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;P.S. — Thanks to Zach P. for asking for this info and prompting me to make this page. Also thanks to Brooke and Abe for adding fuel to the flame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr class=&quot;major&quot; /&gt;

&lt;!-- Content --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;Intro Package (3 sessions)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Each session is 90 minutes and can be in person or by phone. The average amount of time between each session is about 4 weeks but you can have more or less time depending on your needs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;4u 12u$(medium)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;1: Scratching the surface&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This session is largely about surfacing your current reality. I'll ask lots of questions and you'll do lots of talking. I'll ask you things about how your day-to-day life and where (and how) you want to be in the future. In the process, I'll share a little bit about what I see and we'll identify a 1-3 areas to work on.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;4u 12u$(medium)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;2: Digging in&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;After having some time (2-8 weeks) to run with those areas we picked out, we'll check in about how things went! Based on that and things I heard in the first session, I'll share more tips, tools, and theory about how to work towards personal change. We'll tweak your list of experiments and then set our sights on session 3.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;4u$ 12u$(medium)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;3: Learning from experiments&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In this session, we'll review how the 2nd round of experiments went. Then, having done two loops of experimentation, we'll reflect on how you **actually** change (or don't!). After thinking through that, we'll brainstorm how to incorporate those lessons to support other changes you want to make. I'll also ask you for a little feedback on the whole process.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;actions&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;button special&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1sxujZckhY8eIfNRIc_MlCGRGsrQ9t5slfItcBJCF92w/edit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See Rate Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr class=&quot;major&quot; /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;Other Offerings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;6u 12u$(small)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Tune up / Check in&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;If you've done the Intro package, we can do a 60 minute tune up/check in at any time (schedules allowing, of course). These are helpful if you want a medium amount of support figuring out how to work through a specific block or barrier in your change processes.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul class=&quot;actions&quot;&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;button special disabled&quot;&gt;$55-220&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;6u$ 12u$(small)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Personal Systems Consult&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;If we've never worked together before, but you're not interested in the Intro package, this could be for you. In a single 2-hour session, I'll assess how your personal systems work and how you think about them. Then I'll share a bunch of relevant theory, tips, and tools. I'll also put together a list of resources for you to dig into.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul class=&quot;actions&quot;&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;button special&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1sxujZckhY8eIfNRIc_MlCGRGsrQ9t5slfItcBJCF92w/edit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See Rate Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr class=&quot;major&quot; /&gt;


&lt;!-- Elements --&gt;
&lt;!-- &lt;h2 id=&quot;elements&quot;&gt;Experimental Offerings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are offerings that I'm starting to experiment with. Until I get them fine tuned, pricing is negotiable. Help me help other folks (and yourself) by trying these out with me!&lt;/p&gt; --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;6u 12u$(medium)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Annual Retreat&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Each year for the past several years, I've gone on &lt;a href=&quot;https://lqb2.github.io/blog/2016/12/23/my-personal-retreat-long-version/&quot;&gt;an annual retreat&lt;/a&gt; to prep for the next year. In 2020, Maureen White and I launched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.2020vision.space/&quot;&gt;2020 vision&lt;/a&gt;: a retreat that supported 10 folks to vision for their year. Sign up for the mailing list there to get notified if we decide to offer it again.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul class=&quot;actions&quot;&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;button special disabled&quot;&gt;$750-1600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;  
    &lt;div class=&quot;6u 12u$(medium)&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Cohort Coaching&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Interested in the Intro Package but want to come with a buddy (or 2 or 3)? I'm testing out how to support groups of 2-4 people to go through a series of 3 sessions together. There will be less attention on each individual, but having a built-in support structure and other people to learn with/from can be worth the tradeoff.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;H/T to DCC at &lt;a href=&quot;http://infinitegrowth.rocks/&quot;&gt;Infinite Growth&lt;/a&gt; for this cohort idea.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul class=&quot;actions&quot;&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;button special disabled&quot;&gt;$150-450 / session&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr class=&quot;major&quot; /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;A Note about Pricing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also committed to getting compensated what I think the work is worth and I'm really interested in making this work available to everyone. Therefore, I offer coaching using a sliding scale &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; I love bartering. I am especially excited to barter outputs that come up in the process of the coaching itself... For example, one person I worked with wanted to do more pottery. I helped them restructure their time and energy to spend more time on pottery. Instead of cash, they gave me pots. Not only did they spend more time on pottery, but I got some dope pots that I am still using today and they are more confident about their pottery! I love working out arrangements like this. Partial trades are on the table, too. I take payment in cash, via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paypal.me/lqb2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;PayPal&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://venmo.com/lawrence-barrinerii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Venmo&lt;/a&gt; , and am happy to structure whatever payment plan works for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/section&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- 

**Testimonials**

_Coming soon..._


---

For more info, please see my [bio](http://lqb2.co/about) or [my online CV](http://lqb2.co/online-cv/). If you prefer a customized résumé, please ask. 

 --&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/coaching.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/coaching.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
